Frank Juval Quinones

SUMMARY

Entrepreneurial, creative professional experienced in taking projects from concept to finished product, while ensuring solutions meet business needs. Highly experienced with a wide range of technologies while keeping an eye on emerging technologies. Decisiveness and dependability has created trust with leadership.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER/DIGITAL DESIGNER, UNIVERSAL PARKS & RESORTS • 2013-2020

- Took over as design lead for Universal's new Meetings & Events website and managed it to completion
- Managed and developed internal sales application that found success and spread throughout Orlando, Hollywood, and New York
- Created Universal's industry-first chatbot for the parks in Orlando and Hollywood
- · Spearheaded digital experience for annual Harry Potter event at Universal Orlando Resort
- Partnered with various teams as a consultant for creative and tech projects
- Designed and developed Universal's first responsive emails
- · Worked with team members and leadership to oversee roadmaps and long-range plans
- Enlisted team members and leadership to form partnership with UCF Design program
- Mentored team members

WEB DESIGNER, AFFILIATE MANAGER.COM • 2012-2013

- · Designed and developed email marketing, landing pages, and enhancements for client websites
- Built web tools using HTML and CSS
- Managed projects & mentored team members
- Designed trade show collateral

WEB DESIGNER, MARRIOTT VACATION CLUB • 2011-2012

- · Designed emails, landing pages, enewsletters, and web site enhancements
- · Led creative reviews, conduct design presentations, mentored team members
- Upheld brand standards
- Developed new UI systems in order to simplify user experience

SR. GRAPHIC DESIGNER, DIGITAL DAYDREAM • 2009-2010

- UI design and front-end development using HTML & CSS
- Wireframing, prototypes, and web site maintenance
- Sourcing photography, creating web graphics, retouching photos, and logo design

PUBLICATIONS ARTIST, VISIT ORLANDO • 2004-2008

- Print design such as posters, trade show collateral, bus signage, magazine ads, postcards, editorial illustrations, etc.
- Web projects such as designing & developing email marketing, landing pages, and enewsletters
- Photography and art direction

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, TUPPERWARE • 2002-2004

- · Used design to maintain Tupperware's brand equity while keeping it contemporary
- · Art direction
- · Worked on various print and web projects because of versatility
- · Played a key role in launching their first email and online marketing
- · Relationship building with internal clients
- · Conducted design presentations

GRAPHIC ARTIST, AMES TRUE TEMPER • 2002

- · Art direction
- · Key player in the rebranding of Ames and True Temper after its merger
- · Used design as a means of introducing new and innovative products
- · Conducted design presentations

GRAPHIC ARTIST/ANIMATOR, VARIOUS • 1994-2002

I worked as a graphic artist and animator from 1994 to 2000 in various capacities and various companies such as The Miami Herald; as well as design agencies, and also on a freelance basis.

EDUCATION

Santa Fe College, Gainesville, Florida — A.A.S. in Graphic Design, 1999-2001 University of Central Florida, Orlando Florida — Animation Program, 1997-1998 New World School of the Arts, Miami, Florida — Fine Arts Program, 1994-1996 Miami-Dade College, Miami, Florida — General Education, 1991-1993